Guide to the Dan Miller Photographs Collection PHOTOS.120
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Unions.
  - Subseries I:X: United Food and Commercial Workers, Local 342,.
    - Meat Wrapper Pat Zang - A & P Oreonseile [?], Long Island [Total negs: 21], Apr 24, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11674)
    - Credit Union Story Brooklyn, Jam [?] & Heart [?] [Total negs: 34], Apr 27, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11675)
    - Senior Citizens Annual Dinner Dance - Jamaica [Total negs: 75], May 2, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11676)
    - Softball Dyker Field Brooklyn [Total negs: 23], May 3, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11677)
    - Executive Bd. Certificates [Total negs: 31], May 12, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11678)
    - Grand Union Jamaica [Total negs: 36], May 18, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11679)
    - Blood Bank Twin Oaks, Huntington[?] [Total negs: 35], May 18, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11680)
    - Drugs Brooklyn Office [Total negs: 27], May 20, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11681)
    - Softball Awards Jamaica [Total negs: 24], Jul 20, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11682)
    - Safety Committee Union & Management Jamaica [Total negs: 24], Aug 31, 1970 (Box 11, Item 11683)
- Series II: Labor Organizations.
  (Note that in the container list below, shoot numbers are listed in the column for "item.")
  - Building and Construction Trades Council [Total negs: 91], Oct 21, 1970 (Box 8, Item 11580)
  - Building and Construction Trades Council [Total negs: 50], Sep 21, 1988 (Box 9, Item 11620)